

♥ Viet Nam chaudanghuy@gmail.com +84768567579

Links

Github

Skills

Git

Docker

Linux
PHP
Python
SQL
MongoDB
JavaScript
React
Node.js

Profile

Full Stack Engineer with 10 years of experience. Willing to relocate

Experienced web developer with a strong background in developing applications for a diverse clientele. Passionate about building world class web applications and self-motivated to meet deadlines while collaborating effectively as part of a larger team.

Strong organizational skills, including the ability to balance multiple projects and manage time efficiently

Employment History

May 2019 — Present

Full-stack Software Engineer at BESMARTEE

- Strong organisational and project management skills.
- · Proficiency with fundamental front end languages.
- · Excellent verbal communication skills.
- Develop software based on approved design.
- · Integrate with third-party APIs.
- · Build high-quality, scalable and robust software

Sep 2017 — May 2019

Team Lead at BAOLAU PTE LTD

- Wear many hats including customer support and development team
- Keeps the team in line with all activities and task prioritization.
- Resolve conflict or miscommunication that may arise to avoid any negative impact on team collaboration.
- Develop efficient, well-structured functions in kick-starter phrase
- Determines goals and objectives at the beginning of the project until it is accomplished.
- · Code review and enroll hiring new member

Jul 2016 — Aug 2017

Senior Backend Developer at PROPZY

- Design & develop web applications and maintain existing web applications by using Laravel
- Design and implement RESTful APIs for Real Estate

 Platform
- Perform UI tests to optimize performance
- Collaborate with Front-end developers to integrate user-facing elements with Propzy platforms
- Build reusable code and libraries for future use
- · Provide training junior developers and code review
- · Enroll hiring

Oct 2014 — Jun 2016

Senior PHP Developer at YRGLM

- Implementation of application and implementation of Marketing Platform.
- Developing and maintenance modules for marketing systems.
- · Optimize database
- · Support training for members and code review

Feb 2012 — Aug 2014

Backend Developer at GAMELOFT

- Integrate WAP sites, Web Services to Gameloft Ecommerce System
- Implement promotions and other tools to increase game sales
- Maintain, document and offer support on the sites and services in Southeast Asia
- Offer software solutions for data acquisition systems and management tools for business needs in terms of advertising.

Jun 2010 — Aug 2011

Junior PHP Developer at AOTHUN

- Build ERP system
- Maintenance and develop new services/modules for business
- Ensure product quality Research new technologies and libraries
- Consult head department new solution for troubleshooting performance, E-commerce promos, System Improvement.
- Self-learning for mobile app

Education

2005 - 2009

Houston Community College

Bachelor of Applied Science (BASc)

Computer Science

References

References available upon request